http://www.ocscsailing.com/privacy

Supplemental Study Halls
Are You a Beginner?
Beginning sailors, let us show you the best way to start sailing with us on the SF Bay.
View Our Basic Keelboat Course.
Boat Yacht Ownership
With us, you’ll have a good friend and trusted partner in the yachting industry.
Learn About Our Boat Ownership Program.
Club Membership
An OCSC membership is a terrific investment in your sailing career and social life.
Come Join the Club!
Wednesday Night Sail
Set sail and enjoy an relaxing night out on the Bay, skippered by a professional OCSC skipper.
Greece Flotilla
Continue the seafarers’ tradition of thousands of years with an Aegean adventure under sail.
Find out more.
Angel Island Adventure
Build your team with an exciting scenic, and challenging sail to San Francisco’s Angel Island.
Book This Team Adventure
View Cart
Your shopping cart is empty.
Advanced Celestial Navigation
Are You a Beginner?
Beginning sailors, let us show you the best way to start sailing with us on the SF Bay.
View Our Basic Keelboat Course.
Boat Yacht Ownership
With us, you’ll have a good friend and trusted partner in the yachting industry.
Learn About Our Boat Ownership Program.
Club Membership
An OCSC membership is a terrific investment in your sailing career and social life.
Come Join the Club!
Wednesday Night Sail
Set sail and enjoy an relaxing night out on the Bay, skippered by a professional OCSC skipper.
Greece Flotilla
Continue the seafarers’ tradition of thousands of years with an Aegean adventure under sail.
Find out more.
Angel Island Picnic
Why Bring Your Team Sailing?
Angel Island Adventure
Build your team with an exciting scenic, and challenging sail to San Francisco’s Angel Island.
Book This Team Adventure
We're closed until shelter in place is ended.
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Data Security statement
Protecting your personal information is a top priority at OCSC Sailing.  We use Secure Sockets Layer(SSL) technology through Verisign to protect your online order information.  Every day, Verisign intelligent infrastructure services enable and protect billions of interactions across the worlds’s voice and data networks.  When you provide your credit card number, SSL encrypts all personal information, including your card number, name and address assuring the security of your personal information.
Shipping Policy
We ship UPS or US Mail ground.  Customer may, for extra expense, specify the shipping method.
Refund Policy
For refund policies of our different products, please refer to those products’ sections of the website.
Proprietary Rights Restrictions
All material on the OCSC Sailing (hereafter known as "OCSC") website (the "Site"), including without limitation all informational text, photographs, graphics, audio, video, messages, files, documents, images or other materials (collectively, the "Materials"), whether publicly posted or privately transmitted, as well as all derivative works, is owned by OCSC ("We", "Us") or other parties that have licensed their Materials to OCSC and is protected by copyright, trademark and other intellectual property laws. OCSC disclaims any proprietary interest in trademarks, service marks, logos, slogans, domain names and trade names other than its own. Trademarks, logos, images and service marks displayed on the Site are the property of either OCSC or other third parties. You may not copy, reproduce, republish, modify, download, post, transmit, or distribute in any way any Material from the Site, including code and software, without the prior written permission of OCSC or the respective owner of such marks.
The Materials on the Site may not be copied, reproduced, republished, downloaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way, including by email or other electronic means. Any modification of the Materials, use of the Materials on any website or networked computer environment, or use of the Materials for any purpose other than personal, non-commercial use is a violation of the copyright, trademark, and other proprietary rights in the Materials and is expressly prohibited. Additionally, the use of any device, software or routine that interferes or attempts to interfere with the proper working of the Site is expressly prohibited.
Please note that We assume no responsibility for reviewing unsolicited ideas for our business, such as product or advertising ideas, and will not incur any liability as a result of any similarities that may appear in future OCSC products or services. By submitting Materials or ideas, you waive any right to compensation of any type for the Materials or ideas. Any and all rights to Materials and ideas submitted to Us become the exclusive property of OCSC.
Links to Other Websites
If any link is offered connecting you to a third party website, it is as an accommodation to the respective third party site owner and without charge. Websites linked to and from this Site are not necessarily under the control of OCSC and we will have no responsibilities or liabilities whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any such linked site or any link or linking program at any time. OCSC does not necessarily endorse companies (or related products or services) whose sites are linked to or from this Site. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to this Site, you do so entirely at your own risk.
Disclaimer of Warranties
THE SITE AND THE CONTENTS HEREIN ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE," AND ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, ARE DISCLAIMED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, QUIET ENJOYMENT, NON-INFRINGEMENT AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR DAMAGE OR LOSS CAUSED BY ERRORS ON THE SITE, CONTENT ON THE SITE OR THE INTERNET. ADDITIONALLY, THE SITE MAY BE UNAVAILABLE UNEXPECTEDLY AS A RESULT OF ERRORS OR CIRCUMSTANCES BEYOND OUR CONTROL.
Privacy Statement
At OCSC, your personal privacy and the security of your personal information are of primary concern. Under no circumstances will OCSC sell or share any personal information about you to or with any person or organization except those authorized by you, or as may be required by law or court order. By providing an email address, you give us permission to follow up with e-newsletters and other electronic correspondence. We do not sell or exchange any email addresses.
Further Questions If you have any questions or comments about our Legal Notice, please contact us.
